[
   {
     question_text : "Round robin scheduling is essentially the preemptive version of ________ ?",
     questionId : 1,
     answer : 1,
     options : ["FIFO","SJF","Shortest remaining","Longest time first"]
   },
   {
     question_text : "A page fault occurs ?",
     questionId : 2,
     answer : 1,
     options : ["when the page is not in the memory",
"when the page is in the memory",
"when the process enters the blocked state",
"when the process is in the ready state"]
   },
   {
     question_text : "Which of the following will determine your choice of systems software for your computer? ",
     questionId : 3,
     answer : 4,
     options : ["Is the applications software you want to use compatible with it ?",
"Is it expensive ?",
"Is it compatible with your hardware ?",
"Both 1 and 3"]
   },
    { question_text : "What is a shell ? ",
     questionId : 4,
     answer : 2,
     options : ["is a hardware component",
"It is a command interpreter",
"It is a part in compiler",
"It is a tool in CPU scheduling"]
   },
     {question_text : "Routine is not loaded until it is called. All routines are kept on disk in a relocatable load format. The main program is loaded into memory & is executed. This type of loading is called... ? ",
     questionId : 5,
     answer : 3,
     options : ["Static loading",
"Dynamic loading",
"Dynamic linking",
"Overlays"]
   },
     {question_text : "In the blocked state ? ",
     questionId : 6,
     answer : 1,
     options : ["the processes waiting for I/O are found",
"the process which is running is found",
"the processes waiting for the processor are found",
"none of the above"]
   },
     {question_text : "What is the memory from 1K - 640K called ?",
     questionId : 7,
     answer : 4,
     options : ["Extended Memory",
"Normal Memory",
"Low Memory",
"Conventional Memory"]
   },
  {   question_text : "Virtual memory is ..... ?",
     questionId : 8,
     answer : 3,
     options : ["An extremely large main memory",
"An extremely large secondary memory",
"An illusion of extremely large main memory",
"A type of memory used in super computers"]
   },
   {  question_text : "Which is not the state of the process ?",
     questionId : 9,
     answer : 4,
     options : ["Blocked",
"Running",
"Ready",
"Privileged"]
   },
    { question_text : "The number of processes completed per unit time is known as.... ?",
     questionId : 10,
     answer : 2,
     options : ["Output",
"Throughput",
"Efficiency",
"Capacity"]
   }
  
   ]
